Simon Fraser University Library fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Tri Universities Libraries (TRIUL) records, 1970 - 1989; F-50-12; 47 cm of textual records; Tri-Universities Libraries
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 2, 1976; F-50-12-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-111)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 1, 1977; F-50-12-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-111)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 2, 1977; F-50-12-0-0-24 (Archival box - small 50-112)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, 1979 - 1980; F-50-12-0-0-25 (Archival box - small 50-112)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, 1980; F-50-12-0-0-26 (Archival box - small 50-112)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, 1989; F-50-12-0-0-27 (Archival box - small 50-112)